http://www.northpole.com/privacy.asp

CLOSE X
We need your help, friend! Since 1996 Northpole.com has been making your holidays magical with loads of fun activities, including letters to Santa. This site has always been completely free, and due to the rising overhead costs every year, we have to ask for your assistance to keep Northpole.com running.
Would you pitch in $3? For less than the cost of a peppermint mocha, you can truly help. Thank you!
Help via PayPal
Pitch in $3 - $3.00 USD
Pitch in $5 - $5.00 USD
Pitch in $10 - $10.00 USD
Pitch in $25 - $25.00 USD
Pitch in $50 - $50.00 USD
Pitch in $100 - $100.00 USD
Supporter Frequently Asked Questions    •    Supporter Privacy Policy
Hello!
Sign Up  •  Log In
This Privacy Policy is updated as of December 3, 2018.
I. INTRODUCTION
Northpole Productions, LLC (“Northpole.com,” “We,” or “Us”) recognizes that those who use our services (“you” or “users”) value their privacy. We want you to know that your privacy is important to us too, and have provided this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the services we provide. This document outlines important information on how we collect, use, and disclose information gathered on our website, located at www.northpole.com (the “Site”), and through any features, materials, promotions, or other services (including co-branded or affiliated services) that may be offered by Northpole.com or its affiliates (collectively “the Services”). Your use of the Services, as well as information provided during such use, are subject to the Northpole.com Terms of Use. By using the Services, you are consenting to the Terms of Use, and to the information collection and use practices provided in this Privacy Policy. Both the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy may be updated by Northpole.com from time to time.
If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at privacy@northpole.com or by mail to the following address:
Northpole Productions, LLC
1300 Ridenour Blvd NW
Suite 210
Kennesaw, GA 30152
USA
II. INFORMATION WE COLLECT
A. User Provided Information
By choosing to register for an account on the Site and using the Services, you provide certain personal information to Northpole.com, which we collect. This information may generally include the following:
Biographic information, such as your name
Your email address, and any other contact information you choose to submit
Your user ID and preferences
Any communications you send to Northpole.com
Submissions to any Northpole.com or affiliate promotions, contests, or competitions
Your subscription to any newsletters or services offered by Northpole.com
Any other information you submit to us through the course of your participation in the Services
B. Cookies
When you visit Northpole.com’s website, we may send one or more cookies to your computer, or other device. These cookies are small files that enable us or others to identify your unique browser. Northpole.com uses both session cookies, which are temporary files that typically disappear when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which remains on your computer or device after your browser is closed and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. You can remove persistent cookies from your computer or device by following the directions provided in the help file of your web browser. You may also be able to reset your web browser to refuse all cookies, or to indicate when a cookie is being sent to your computer or device. Please note, however, that some features of the Site and Services require cookies to function. Disabling your device’s ability to accept cookies could prevent these features from functioning properly.
C. Log Files
When you access Northpole.com’s website or the Services, your computer or device sends information that may be automatically recorded by our servers. These server logs can include information such as your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, platform type, and browser type and language. Server logs can also include information on your visit to the Site, including the domain names of websites visited, landing pages, the order in which you viewed pages and the amount of time you spent on those pages, your web or app request and the date and time of that request, and one or more cookies that identify your unique browser.
D. Clear GIFs
Northpole.com may utilize technology such as clear GIFs, also known as web beacons. Such technology is used to track the online usage patterns of your use of the Services. We may also use such technology to collect data on HTML-based emails sent by Northpole.com to track which emails are opened by users.
III. HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
A. General Use
In general, Northpole.com uses the personal information you submit to provide and maintain the Services you use, and to aid us in serving you better. This general use includes the following:
To facilitate the creation and security of your account on the Site
To identify you as a user and to provide you with our products and services
To allow you to personalize your use of the Services, and to improve the quality of your experience with our Site and Services
To process and respond to inquiries and requests that you may send us
To alert you regarding special events or promotions, new products, or new features of the Services
To alert you regarding any non-promotional changes or updates to the Site or Services, or other administrative matters
To send newsletters, surveys, or other promotional materials related to our Services
To enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Services, and to maintain compliance with any applicable law or regulation
B. Marketing Content
Northpole.com may utilize the information you provide in order to send you marketing content and advertisements regarding our products and services. This includes products and services provided by Northpole.com in which you may be interested, provided that you have not requested otherwise. This may also include marketing content and advertisements for products and services that we market on behalf of a third party, provided that you have not requested otherwise. Marketing or advertising content may be sent by Northpole.com via multiple channels, including email, direct mail, display media, and push notifications.
C. Experience Improvement
Northpole.com uses the information you provide to improve your experience with our Site and Services. We may store and track user information, such as usage trends and user preferences, to improve the quality, security, or design of our Site and Services. We may also use such information to create new features, services, and promotions for users.
D. Cookies
Northpole.com uses session and persistent cookies, log files, and clear GIFs to provide personalized content for our users, and to retain information so that users do not have to re-enter it for subsequent uses of the Site or Services. Northpole.com also uses this technology to track and analyze the effectiveness of advertisements and marketing campaigns, and to track aggregate metrics such as web traffic to our Site.
E. Additional Use of Information
Northpole.com may anonymize and aggregate your personal information to create data to be used for any legitimate business purpose. By anonymizing and aggregating the information, the data collected does not personally identify you. This data may be used for legitimate reporting, research, and advertising purposes.
IV. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
Northpole.com does not use a child’s online information for any purpose other than responding directly to the child’s request. Northpole.com does not distribute any child’s personally identifiable information to third parties for any reason, nor give children the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information.
V. INTERACTION WITH THIRD PARTY SITES AND SERVICES
Northpole.com may work with third party companies to collect data on the Services for analytical purposes. This data is collected through cookies and other automated means and, in some cases, may be maintained by the third party company.
VI. WHEN WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION
A. Ordinary Use
Northpole.com may disclose the information we collect from you to our subsidiaries, affiliates, or service providers who process your information on our behalf as part of your use of the Site and Services. This can include billing and payment processing, web hosting, email services, customer and technical support, and marketing and promotional services. The agreements and contracts in place with all of our subsidiaries, affiliates, and service providers limit the types of information such entities can access and process, and require them to use reasonable efforts at all times to keep your personal information secure.
B. Necessary Disclosures
Northpole.com reserves the right to share personal information where we, in good faith, believe that such disclosure is necessary for any of the following reasons:
To enforce the Northpole.com Terms of Use
To avoid liability, damage, or harm
To investigate any valid third party claim
To respond to any official request or court order
To comply with any applicable local, state, or Federal law or regulation
To protect the security and integrity of the Site and Services
To protect the security, rights, and safety or Northpole.com, our users, and others
C. Additional Disclosures
There may be a disclosure of your personal information to another entity in the event that Northpole.com is involved in a merger, sale, or acquisition. Information may also be disclosed in the event that Northpole.com is involved in a reorganization, bankruptcy, or receivership where the application of law or equitable principle affecting creditors’ rights requires it, or otherwise requires a change of company control.
VII. INFORMATION SECURITY
Northpole.com is committed to protecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. We employ a variety of technologies and procedures to help ensure that your personal information is protected from any unauthorized disclosure, access, or use. While neither we, nor any organization, can guarantee the total security of information provided and processed online, Northpole.com takes specific and appropriate measures to ensure that your information is protected. This includes reserving the right to take measure to verify your identity before allowing you access to your profile, or any feature of the Services. We ask that you assist us in our effort to protect your information by keeping your password and account information secret at all times.
VIII. YOUR CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION
A. Email Communications
Northpole.com may periodically send you free newsletters or other emails about products and services. At any time you may request that you stop receiving further such communications from us by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the email you receive. Please note that, regardless of whether you unsubscribe from marketing emails, we may send you service related communications, including notices of updates to our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services will serve as proof of your acceptance of such updates terms and policies.
B. Updating your Personal Information
You may change your personal information at any time by logging into your Northpole.com account via the Site and Services. You can also log into your account to update your marketing preferences, including whether you would like to subscribe or unsubscribe to newsletters sent by Northpole.com.
C. Right to Remove or Request Data
If you wish to delete your Northpole.com account, you can do so at any time. Simply log in to your account. On your account dashboard, click on the Edit Account button, then click the “Delete My Account” link at the bottom of the page.
Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), visitors located in the EU have the right to request their personal data. If you wish to request your data, contact us here, selecting “Data Retrieval Request” as the topic.
IX. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California residents are entitled to request certain general information regarding Northpole.com’s disclosure of their personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please write to us at the following address:
Northpole Productions, LLC
1300 Ridenour Blvd NW
Suite 210
Kennesaw, GA 30152
X. CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically, which will be reflected by the “Last update posted” date, above. We ask that you please revisit this page so that you remain aware of any changes to this Privacy Policy. If a revision is made to the Privacy Policy that is determined, by our sole discretion, to be material, we will notify users by contacting them through the email address associated with their account. Your continued use of the Services will serve as proof of your acceptance of such updates terms and policies.
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy, please email us at privacy@northpole.com.
© 1996–2020 Northpole Productions, LLC
About
Contact
FAQs
Credits
Banners
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Support Northpole.com
Northpole.com uses cookies.
This website uses cookies to improve user experience. By continuing to use our website, you consent to all cookies in accordance with our Privacy Policy.
Got It.
